[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Casablanca, what is the last name of the character portrayed by actress Ingrid Bergman, Ilsa?", "correct_answer": "Lund", "incorrect_answers": ["Lang", "Liszt", "Lindstrom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were Anthony, Skip and Jose delivering at the beginning of the movie Dead Presidents?", "correct_answer": "milk", "incorrect_answers": ["newspapers", "mail", "packages"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Marianas Trench, the deepest location on the surface of the Earths crust, lies in this ocean.", "correct_answer": "The Pacific Ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["The Southern Ocean", "The Indian Ocean", "The Atlantic Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What method of preparation is used for the popular snack from Indonesia called Krupuk?", "correct_answer": "Deep frying", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Baking", "Boiling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Scandinavian mythology this is the equivalent of the apocalypse.", "correct_answer": "ragnarok", "incorrect_answers": ["rekjavak", "odinthorisagak", "rasnajivarak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first known use, in English, of the word orange in reference to a color was by this man.", "correct_answer": "King Henry Vlll", "incorrect_answers": ["Warren Alfred VI", "King JamesII", "Devin Knight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This European island is situated in the North Atlantic Ocean, south of the Arctic Circle. Its largest city is Reykjavik.", "correct_answer": "Iceland", "incorrect_answers": ["Ireland", "Greenland", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In physics and chemistry, which isotopes are considered stable?", "correct_answer": "Isotopes that are not radioactive", "incorrect_answers": ["Isotopes that are in a bond", "Isotopes in which the number of electrons, protons and neutrons is equal", "Isotopes that do not form bonds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Phreatic eruptions occur when the temperature of magma is relatively low and it solidifies very quickly, sometimes blocking the vent of the volcano.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Helminthophobia is the fear of what?", "correct_answer": "of being infested with worms", "incorrect_answers": ["of scientific terminology", "of not going to heaven", "of seeing blood or bloody objects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much does human hair grow in a year?", "correct_answer": "9 inches", "incorrect_answers": ["7 inches", "12 inches", "4 inches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cacti can only be pollinated by a certain type of tropical bees.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]